CHRISTOPHER PERET

CONTACT

Email: cperet89@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/c-peret

Phone: 262-893-8446

Residence: Las Vegas, NV 89102

SKILLS

• Software Developer:

Python, JavaScript, SQL, Git, HTML5, CSS, C++, MongoDB, Express, React.js, NodeJs, Bash, Visual Basic

- Modern Full-Stack
- Classic front end
- REST API development
- Middleware / Routing
- Database Management
- Scrum Master / VCS
- Agile Environments

• Automation Programmer:

Metasys, BAC-net, SIEMENS, Allen-Bradley, SCADA, CCT, LCT, PLC, Visio, P&ID

• Soft-Skills

- Team Management
- Project Planning
- Project Supervision
- Instructor
- System Design
- Strategic Solutions
- Integration
- Communication
- Co-ordination.
- Self-Motivated
- Adaptability

REFERENCES

Dr. M Chasco – Matlab – Collaborator (262) 565-7577 (Inquire for more)

EDUCATION

UC Berkeley – Computer Science - Berkeley, CA **Steamfitters Local 601 Apprenticeship** - Milwaukee 04/2014

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Developer with <u>13 years</u> background as a Senior Automation Specialist and Programmer. Experienced Instructor and Mentor. <u>7 Years of Team Management</u>, Co-ordination, and Project planning experience. Dedicated to research and ongoing skill development. **Versatile**, **adaptive**, asset that understands and implements highly complex and nuanced solutions for the situation. Well-practiced in thoroughly testing and commissioning solutions; Identifying and correcting "edge case" scenarios. Focused on detailed and nuanced solutions while utilizing best practice. Expert at <u>effectively communicating highly technical concepts to students, teammates, clients and <u>customers.</u></u>

WORK HISTORY

Software Developer, 11/2022 to Current

- Las Vegas, NV

Building Automation Controls Developer, 07/2020 to 11/2022 **University Wisconsin Milwaukee** - Milwaukee, Wi

- Develop, Modify, Document and Commission logic on controller and network Level.
- Solve and debug engine/server level software/database issues.
- Monitor, troubleshoot and diagnose active multi building/campus scale HVAC Building Automation and Power/Utility Systems.
- UI/UX Development
- OEM application integration

Building Automation Controls Instructor, 09/2020 to 01/2022 **Local 601** - Milwaukee, WI

Organized, created, and taught curriculum for Building Automation Controls apprentices in south east Wisconsin area.

Various (inquire), 04/2009 – 09/2020 **Local 601**- SE Wisconsin